<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Authors:
* Ajeje Brazorf
* Amire80
* Fitoschido
* Fs00
* Kelson
* Liuxinyu970226
* McDutchie
* MohitMali
* Robby
* Shirayuki
* Stephane
* Tacsipacsi
* The RedBurn
* Verdy p
-->
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools" tools:ignore="all">
  <string name="menu_help">{{Identical|Help}}</string>
  <string name="menu_home">{{Identical|Home}}</string>
  <string name="menu_settings">{{Identical|Settings}}</string>
  <string name="menu_search_in_text">This is for finding all words on the current page, which contain the current search string.</string>
  <string name="bookmarks">{{Identical|Bookmark}}</string>
  <string name="menu_random_article">{{Identical|Random article}}</string>
  <string name="menu_full_screen">{{Identical|Full screen}}</string>
  <string name="menu_exit_full_screen">This is for the content description of ImageButton, this is showing when the user reads the article in full-screen mode, by clicking on this ImageButton full-screen mode will close.</string>
  <string name="menu_read_aloud">This is for the MenuItem button text, by clicking on this button we are starting to read the current page text with \"Text to speech\" functionality.</string>
  <string name="menu_read_aloud_stop">This is for the MenuItem button text, when the \"Read aloud (Text to speech is reading the current page data)\" and if the user clicks on this button \"Text to speech\" will stop reading the current page data.</string>
  <string name="menu_support_kiwix">This is for the \"Navigation Item\" button text on the main page of the \"Kiwix app\", clicking on this button leads to opening the \"Kiwix support\" website page.</string>
  <string name="menu_wifi_hotspot">* English : it maps to some \"hotspot\" feature in order to serve collections of contents (aka books) over a local network area.\n* French : il s’agit de la fonctionnalité \'\'hotspot\'\' : l’anglais \'\'host books\'\' n’est pas particulièrement satisfaisant à la base.</string>
  <string name="save_media">This appears in a dialog window when we long-click on any image/pdf/video. By clicking on this button, it will save the data into phone storage.</string>
  <string name="save_media_error">This error message shows to the user in an \"Android Toast\", when there is an error while saving the file in phone storage.</string>
  <string name="save_media_saved">This appears in an \"Android Toast\" when a file is successfully saved in the \"Downloads/org.kiwix/\" directory of the phone storage. Here \"%s\" will be replaced by the saved file name on runtime.</string>
  <string name="search_label">{{Identical|Search}}</string>
  <string name="choose_file">This is a text message to inform the user please select a file .zim file.</string>
  <string name="open_in_new_tab">This message appears in a dialog window when a user long clicks on any URL/pageURL on the current page. This message is to indicate to the user if he wants to open the current URL in a new window.</string>
  <string name="hotspot_service_channel_name">Name of the notification channel used for the hotspot persistent notification.\nCan be found in Android notification settings for Kiwix app.</string>
  <string name="hotspot_failed_title">It is the dialog\'s title to notify the user when there is a failure in starting the hotspot.</string>
  <string name="hotspot_failed_message">It is the dialog\'s message to notify the user to turn off the hotspot.</string>
  <string name="go_to_wifi_settings_label">This message appears in a Dialog window as a dialog button when the user tries to host books on the \"Kiwix server\" but there is no wifi and hotspot available. By clicking on this dialog button user will navigate to the phone\'s wifi settings.</string>
  <string name="connection_refused">This message appears in the \"Android toast\" when the user tries to connect with another user via \"wifi P2P sharing\" to share ZIM files over wifi, but he refuses to connect.</string>
  <string name="hotspot_running">This appears in \"Android Notification\" as a notification description. When the user hosts their book on the \"Kiwix server\" to read books on their PC via wifi/hotspot from their phone.</string>
  <string name="no_books_selected_toast_message">This message appears in \"Android Toast\" as a warning message when the user tries to host their books on the \"Kiwix server\" but there are no books selected for hosting on the server.</string>
  <string name="server_failed_message">This message appears in \"Android Toast\" as a warning message when the user tries to host their books on the \"Kiwix server\" but the hotspot is off. So this message is to notify the user first on your hotspot then try to host their books.</string>
  <string name="server_failed_toast_message">This message appears in \"Android Toast\" as a warning message when there is an error while starting the \"Kiwix server\". So by this message, we are notifying the user server couldn\'t start at this moment.</string>
  <string name="server_started_successfully_toast_message">This message appears in \"Android Toast\" to inform the user when the \"Kiwix server\" successfully hosts their books.</string>
  <string name="server_stopped_successfully_toast_message">This message appears in \"Android Toast\" to inform the user when the \"Kiwix server\" stop.</string>
  <string name="hotspot_turned_on">This is dialog\'s title which informs the user that your hotspot is turned on.</string>
  <string name="hotspot_details_message">Do not change:\n* &lt;code&gt;%1$s&lt;/code&gt; (replaced by the “SSID” value identifying the WiFi hotspot identity for users)\n* &lt;code&gt;%2$s&lt;/code&gt; (replaced by the password or code configured in the hotspot to authorize the association and network connection)</string>
  <string name="server_textview_default_message">This message appears in the \"Wifi Hotspot\" screen as a text message. In the Wifi Hotspot screen, there are all the Zim files are showing which are in the user\'s device and the user can select which book he wants to host on the \"Kiwix server\", so by this message we are informing the user he can select the zim files which he want to host on the server.</string>
  <string name="progress_dialog_starting_server">This message appears in \"Android ProgressDialog\" when the user tries to host the books on the \"Kiwix server\". This message is showing to tell the user, the server is preparing to start.</string>
  <string name="hotspot_dialog_title">This the title displayed when a user clicks wants to start the server in the host books section</string>
  <string name="wifi_dialog_title">This message appears in \"Android Dialog\" when the user tries to host their books on the \"Kiwix server\". By this message, we inform the user there is wifi connected to his phone.</string>
  <string name="wifi_dialog_body">This message appears in the \"Android Dialog\" when the user tries to run the \"Kiwix server\" via WiFi. This message informs the user, to ensure that all the devices are connected to the same Wifi network to view books on all other devices using this service.</string>
  <string name="hotspot_dialog_message">This is used in the dialog while starting a server to host books to tell the user how exactly to proceed</string>
  <string name="hotspot_dialog_neutral_button">This is used in the start server dialog on pressing which the server starts if user has followed the prior guidelines</string>
  <string name="hotspot_channel_description">Description of the notification channel used for the hotspot persistent notification.\nCan be found in Android notification settings for Kiwix app, inside the \"Hotspot Service Channel\" details screen.</string>
  <string name="hotspot_notification_content_title">This message appears in \"Android Notification\" to inform the user \"Kiwix server\" is running.</string>
  <string name="start_server_label">This message shows as the button text, by clicking on this button \"Kiwix server\" starts.</string>
  <string name="stop_server_label">This message shows as the button text, by clicking on this button \"Kiwix server\" stops.</string>
  <string name="server_started_message">This message appears in \"Android TextView\" as a text message. When the \"Kiwix server\" is successfully started, in this message %s will be replaced with the IP address on which the server is running. It shows the details of the server IP address to the user.</string>
  <string name="share_host_address">This message is the content description of \"Android ImageView\", this appears when the \"Kiwix server\" is running and the IP address is visible to the user on which server is running. By clicking on this it will share the IP address with other applications.</string>
  <string name="error_file_not_found">This message appears in \"Android Toast\" as an error message when the user tries to open a Zim file but the file was moved to another directory or deleted. So this message informs the user this file could not be found.</string>
  <string name="unable_to_read_zim_file">This message appears in \"Android Toast\" as a error message when our application is unable to read the zim file.</string>
  <string name="zim_not_opened">This message appears in \"Android Toast\" as an error message when the user opens the application and the previously opened zim file was deleted from the phone storage, then we are showing this error message to the user.</string>
  <string name="error_file_invalid">The message appears in \"Android Toast\" as a warning message when the user tries to open a file and that file is not the zim file.</string>
  <string name="error_article_url_not_found">* This message appears in \"Android Toast\" as an error message when \"Kiwix Reader\" is unable to load the given URL.\n* Here %1$s will be replaced by the URL which is failed to load.</string>
  <string name="pref_display_title">{{Identical|Display}}</string>
  <string name="pref_info_title">{{Identical|Information}}</string>
  <string name="pref_info_version">{{Identical|Version}}</string>
  <string name="pref_night_mode">This is part of the preference settings to show the \"Night Mode\" setting.</string>
  <string name="pref_night_mode_summary">This is part of preference settings to show the user if he enables this setting then all the articles will show with inverted colors.</string>
  <string name="pref_back_to_top">{{Identical|Back to top}}</string>
  <string name="pref_back_to_top_summary">This is part of the preference settings it informs the user, by enabling this setting it displays a button while reading articles at the end of the page, and by clicking on that button it will scroll the page to the top.</string>
  <string name="pref_language_title">{{Identical|Language}}</string>
  <string name="pref_language_chooser">{{Identical|Choose language}}</string>
  <string name="pref_credits">This is part of preference settings, by clicking on this text it will show a dialog with the information of contributors who are contributing to this project and also shows the licenses as well.</string>
  <string name="pref_credits_title">{{Identical|Credit}}</string>
  <string name="tts_lang_not_supported">This appears in \"Android Toast\" as an error message when we are opening the ZIM file to read and the language of the articles of that zim file is not supported by the \"Text to Speech\" feature, then we are showing this error message.</string>
  <string name="no_reader_application_installed">This message appears in \"Android Toast\" as an error message when we want to open a pdf or URL in external applications but there is no application installed on the user\'s device to handle this file type.</string>
  <string name="no_email_application_installed">* This message appears in \"Android Toast\" as an error message when the user sends feedback to the \"Kiwix Team\" but there is no application installed on the user\'s device to handle this action.\n* Here %1s will be replaced by the \"Kiwix team Gmail\" at runtime.</string>
  <string name="no_section_info">This appears as a text message when there is no content header found for the article.</string>
  <string name="request_storage">This appears in the \"Android Toast\" to inform the user, please grant storage access to read the zim file from his storage.</string>
  <string name="request_write_storage">This message appears in \"Android Dialog\" to inform the user when he clicks on downloading any zim file, and we do have not permission to write any zim file to his storage. Then we are showing this message to the user to give write access to their storage.</string>
  <string name="clear_recent_and_tabs_history_dialog">This message appears in \"Android Dialog\" when the user clicks on \"clear all history\". Then we are showing this message to the user to confirm he wants to delete all history.</string>
  <string name="delete_recent_search_item">This message appears in \"Android Dialog\" when the user long clicks on the item in the searched list. Then we are showing this message to the user to confirm he wants to delete this item from searched history.</string>
  <string name="pref_clear_all_history_title">A preference setting item text for cleaning all history in the application e.g Page history, bookmarks, etc.</string>
  <string name="pref_clear_all_history_summary">This is the \"clear history\" settings item description it informs the user by clicking this setting he can clear his recent search and tabs history.</string>
  <string name="pref_notes">{{Identical|Notes}}</string>
  <string name="pref_permission">{{Identical|Permissions}}</string>
  <string name="all_history_cleared">This message appears in the \"Android Snackbar\" to inform the user when all history is cleared.</string>
  <string name="pref_clear_all_bookmarks_title">This is the menu item title, by clicking on the menu item triggers deleting the bookmarks.</string>
  <string name="clear_all_history_dialog_title">This message appears in the \"Android Dialog\" to take confirmation from the user if he wants to delete the entire history.</string>
  <string name="share">{{Identical|Share}}</string>
  <string name="selected_file_cab_app_chooser_title">It is the title of the share intent dialog when the share menu item is clicked for sharing zim files.</string>
  <string name="delete">{{Identical|Delete}}</string>
  <string name="cancel">{{identical|Cancel}}</string>
  <string name="delete_specific_search_toast">This message appears in the \"Android Toast\" as an information message when the delete operation is successful for a recent search.</string>
  <string name="hint_contents_drawer_message">This message appears in the \"Android Dialog\" as an information message which informs the user he can swipe left to view the contents of this article.</string>
  <string name="got_it">Button which allows the user to confirm that they understood the related explanation text.\n\n{{Identical|Got it}}</string>
  <string name="did_you_know">{{Identical|Did you know}}</string>
  <string name="undo">{{Identical|Undo}}</string>
  <string name="tab_closed">This message appears in the \"Android Snackbar\" to inform the user that the current tab is closed.</string>
  <string name="tabs_closed">This message appears in the \"Android Snackbar\" to inform the user that all tabs are closed.</string>
  <string name="bookmark_added">This message appears in the \"Android Snackbar\" to inform the user that the bookmark is successfully added.</string>
  <string name="rate_dialog_title">This message appears in \"Android Dialog\" as a dialog title message, which asks the user to give a rating to the application.</string>
  <string name="rate_dialog_msg">* This message appears in \"Android Dialog\" as a dialog message, which asks the user if he enjoys the application experience, then please give a rating to the application.\n* Here %s will be replaced by the app name.</string>
  <string name="rate_dialog_positive">{{Identical|Rate}}</string>
  <string name="no_thanks">{{Identical|No thanks}}</string>
  <string name="rate_dialog_neutral">{{Identical|Later}}</string>
  <string name="open">{{Identical|Open}}</string>
  <string name="bookmark_removed">This message appears in the \"Android Snackbar\" to inform the user that the bookmark is successfully deleted.</string>
  <string name="pref_newtab_background_title">This message appears in the preference settings description, if the user enables this setting then every new tab will open in the background and the user will be on the same page.</string>
  <string name="pref_newtab_background_summary">This message appears in the preference settings description, if the user enables this setting then every new tab will open in the background and the user will be on the same page.</string>
  <string name="pref_extras">This is the label on the preference settings page. which shows as the extra settings list label.</string>
  <string name="new_tab_snack_bar">This message appears in the \"Android Snackbar\" as an information message, it informs the user article is opened in a new tab.</string>
  <string name="search_widget_text">This message appears in the \"Android Widget\" on the home screen of the user\'s device as a title, by clicking on this widget title user will be redirected to the search screen of the application.</string>
  <string name="speech_prompt_text">The placeholder %s refers to the app name.</string>
  <string name="speech_not_supported">This message appears in the \"Android Toast\" as an error message, it tells the user the device does not support the speech inputs.</string>
  <string name="local_zims">{{Identical|Device}}</string>
  <string name="remote_zims">{{Identical|Online}}</string>
  <string name="library">Displayed in application menu</string>
  <string name="delete_zim_body">* This message appears in the \"Android Dialog\" as an information message, this informs the user the selected zim files will be deleted.\n* Here %s will be replaced by the selected zim file names.</string>
  <string name="delete_zims_toast">This message appears in the \"Android Toast\" as an information message, it shows to the user the selected zim files are deleted.</string>
  <string name="no_files_here">This message indicates there are no files in the storage to show in the list.</string>
  <string name="download_no_space">This message shows in the \"Android Snackbar\" to inform users that there is insufficient space in their storage to download the selected zim file.</string>
  <string name="download">The title of the fragment/place where books are downloaded.</string>
  <string name="space_available">This message shows in the \"Android Snackbar\" to inform users how much space is left in their storage when there is insufficient space to download the zim file.</string>
  <string name="zim_simple">{{Identical|Simple}}</string>
  <string name="zim_no_pic">{{Identical|No Pictures}}</string>
  <string name="zim_no_vid">{{Identical|No Videos}}</string>
  <string name="no_network_connection">This appears in TextView as a warning message that there is no internet connection on their device.</string>
  <string name="help_2">This is the title message explaining what Kiwix does. It is showing on the help screen.</string>
  <string name="help_3">This is the description message explaining what Kiwix does. It is showing on the help screen.</string>
  <string name="help_4">It is showing on the help screen. It explains the features of the Kiwix application.</string>
  <string name="help_5">This is a title message for explaining where we are storing the ZIM files. It is showing on the help screen.</string>
  <string name="help_6">This is a descriptive message explaining where the ZIM files are stored. It is showing on the help screen.</string>
  <string name="help_7">This is a descriptive message explaining how many and which type of files are stored on the Kiwix website. It is showing on the help screen.</string>
  <string name="help_8">This is a descriptive message explaining Wikipedia ZIM file is available in how many languages. It is showing on the help screen.</string>
  <string name="help_9">This is a descriptive message explaining other contents are also available to download e.g Wikileaks or Wikisource. It is showing on the help screen.</string>
  <string name="help_10">* This is a descriptive message explaining the downloading steps.\n* It is showing on the help screen.</string>
  <string name="help_11">This is a descriptive message explaining where the Zim files are located after downloading. It is showing on the help screen.</string>
  <string name="pref_storage">{{Identical|Storage}}</string>
  <string name="pref_current_folder">This is showing on the preference settings screen, it shows the currently selected storage in which we are downloading the zim files, whether it is internal or external.</string>
  <string name="delete_zim_failed">This message appears in the \"Android Toast\" as an error message. When there are some files that could not be deleted, due to some reason.</string>
  <string name="tts_pause">{{identical|pause}}</string>
  <string name="tts_resume">{{identical|resume}}</string>
  <string name="stop">{{Identical|Stop}}</string>
  <string name="configure_storage_option">This message appears in the \"Android Dialog\" as an information message. It takes confirmation from the user if he wants to download books in internal storage.</string>
  <string name="internal_storage">{{Identical|Internal}}</string>
  <string name="external_storage">{{Identical|External}}</string>
  <string name="configure">{{Identical|Configure}}</string>
  <string name="yes">{{Identical|Yes}}</string>
  <string name="no">{{Identical|No}}</string>
  <string name="confirm_stop_download_title">This message appears in the \"Android Dialog\" as a confirmation title message. When the user wants to stop the current running download.</string>
  <string name="confirm_stop_download_msg">This message appears in the \"Android Dialog\" as a confirmation description message. When the user wants to stop the current running download, so it takes confirmation from the user.</string>
  <string name="download_change_storage">This message appears in the \"Android Snackbar\" when there is not enough space to download the zim file then this message shows to the user to select secondary storage.</string>
  <string name="tts_not_enabled">This message appears in the \"Android Toast\" as a warning message. When the selected zim file language is not supported by this Text to speech feature, we are informing the user that in this zim file, this feature will not work.</string>
  <string name="texttospeech_initialization_failed">This is an error message showing in the \"Android Toast\". when there is an error in the initialization of text to speech feature.</string>
  <string name="texttospeech_error">This is an error message showing in the \"Android Toast\". when there is an error while reading the zim file text via text to speech feature.</string>
  <string name="next">{{Identical|Next}}</string>
  <string name="previous">{{Identical|Previous}}</string>
  <string name="wifi_only_title">This confirmation message shows in the \"Android Dialog\" when the user tries to download zim files via the mobile network.</string>
  <string name="wifi_only_msg">This confirmation message shows in the \"Android Dialog\" to take confirmation from the user that if he selects the yes he won\'t see this dialog again but he changes this setting from the settings screen.</string>
  <string name="pref_wifi_only">* This message shows in the preference settings screen if the user enables this setting then he can only download the content via wifi.\n* Enable this setting to restrict content downloads to WiFi only.</string>
  <string name="time_day">{{Identical|Day}}</string>
  <string name="time_hour">This message appears while downloading online content to inform the user how much time is left in hours.</string>
  <string name="time_minute">This message appears while downloading online content to inform the user how much time is left in minutes.</string>
  <string name="time_second">This message appears while downloading online content to inform the user how much time is left in seconds.</string>
  <string name="time_left">This is used in a context of “X minutes left” to finish a download.</string>
  <string name="time_today">{{Identical|Today}}</string>
  <string name="time_yesterday">{{Identical|Yesterday}}</string>
  <string name="pref_external_link_popup_title">This message appears in preference settings as a setting title which informs the user when he clicks on the external then it will display a popup.\n\n\'\'\'\"Entering\" should be translated in the sense of \"opening\"/\"accessing\", not \"adding\"/\"inserting\".\'\'\'</string>
  <string name="pref_external_link_popup_summary">This message appears in preference settings as a setting description which informs the user when he clicks on the external then it will display a popup which URLs are not working in the offline mode.</string>
  <string name="external_link_popup_dialog_title">This message appears in the \"Android Dialog\" as a dialog title. When a user clicks on an external link, it informs the user this URL is an external link.\n\n\'\'\'\"Entering\" should be translated in the sense of \"opening\"/\"accessing\", not \"adding\"/\"inserting\".\'\'\'</string>
  <string name="external_link_popup_dialog_message">This message appears in the \"Android Dialog\" as a dialog description when the user tries to open an external link. It informs the user that they will be charged for additional data by opening this URL, or that this URL will not work if the device has no internet connection.\n\n\'\'\'\"Entering\" should be translated in the sense of \"opening\"/\"accessing\", not \"adding\"/\"inserting\".\'\'\'</string>
  <string name="do_not_ask_anymore">This message appears in the \"Android Dialog of External Links\" as a dialog button message. by clicking this button it will not show the \"External Links\" dialog in the future whenever he clicks on the external links.</string>
  <string name="your_languages">A label for language codes field of selected languages, to notify the user which languages he selected.</string>
  <string name="other_languages">{{Identical|Otherlanguages}}</string>
  <string name="no_items_msg">This message appears when there are no items available to show the user.</string>
  <string name="crash_title">This is the title message of the error screen when the application crashes.</string>
  <string name="crash_description">This is the descriptive message when the application crashes, asking the user to provide information about the crash.</string>
  <string name="crash_checkbox_language">This is used in the checkbox to select the reason if the application crashes on the language settings.</string>
  <string name="crash_checkbox_zimfiles">This is used in the checkbox to select the reason if the application crashes on the zim list screen.</string>
  <string name="crash_checkbox_exception">This is used in the checkbox to send the crash details to the Kiwix organization.</string>
  <string name="crash_checkbox_logs">This is used in the checkbox to send the application logs to the Kiwix organization when a crash happens.</string>
  <string name="crash_checkbox_device">This is used in the checkbox to select the device information on which the app crashes e.g on Redmi Note 9 (android 9).</string>
  <string name="crash_button_confirm">This message is used as text, by clicking it will collect all the selected information from the error screen and send it to the Kiwix organization via Gmail.</string>
  <string name="shortcut_disabled_message">This is used for shortcut-disabled messages, which can be found when you enable the kiwix shortcut on your screen.</string>
  <string name="new_tab_shortcut_label">Shortcut item text for opening a new tab.</string>
  <string name="get_content_shortcut_label">This is a shortcut label, by clicking on this shortcut will open the download screen where the user can download the zim files.</string>
  <string name="fav_icon">{{Identical|Favicon}}</string>
  <string name="articleCount">* This appears on the downloaded books as a text, how many articles contains that book.\n* Here %s will be replaced by the articles number e.g 100 articles.</string>
  <string name="get_started">* This is used for button text, which can be found on the welcome screen.\n* By clicking on this button close the welcome screen and opens the main screen of the application.</string>
  <string name="download_books">* This is used as a button label if there are no books found in the user\'s storage.\n* By clicking on this button it will redirect the user to the download screen, where the user can download the book which he wants.</string>
  <string name="humankind_knowledge">This is used in the introduction screen as a text to introduce the feature of the application.</string>
  <string name="welcome_to_the_family">This message appears in the introduction screen, to welcome the user.</string>
  <string name="save_books_offline">* This message appears on the introduction screen, to introduce the app features.\n* They can save the books offline.</string>
  <string name="download_books_message">* This message appears on the introduction screen, to introduce the app features.\n* They can download the books and read them wherever they are whether they have internet or not.</string>
  <string name="unable_to_add_to_bookmarks">This is used in the toast, to inform the user that there is an error in adding the bookmark.</string>
  <string name="go_to_previous_page">* This is used in a content description of the image view.\n* By clicking on this image user navigates to the previously opened page.</string>
  <string name="go_to_next_page">* This is used in a content description of the image view.\n* By clicking on this image user navigates to the next opened page.</string>
  <string name="table_of_contents">* This is used as a content description of the image button.\n* By clicking on this button, a navigation drawer opens that contains a list of contents currently available on the opened page.</string>
  <string name="select_languages">It is shown as the title of the language selection screen.</string>
  <string name="save_languages">It is the title of the menu item which saves the selected languages.</string>
  <string name="send_feedback">It is an option in the help screen which redirects user to send a mail to android@kiwix.org when the option is clicked.</string>
  <string name="expand">{{Identical|Expand}}</string>
  <string name="history">{{Identical|History}}</string>
  <string name="history_from_current_book">* This is used in the switch as a title text, which can be found on the History screen.\n* By enabling this, the user sees the list of all of the books\' history instead of just the last accessed book.</string>
  <string name="search_history">This means \"search in the history of previously visited pages\", \'\'\'so \"search\" is a verb\'\'\'. See https://github.com/kiwix/kiwix-android/issues/1704#issuecomment-576225715</string>
  <string name="selected_items">Toolbar title shown when the user is selecting multiple items in a list. The \"%d\" symbol is replaced with the number of items currently selected.</string>
  <string name="bookmarks_from_current_book">This is used in the switch as a title text, which can be found on the Bookmark screen.\nBy enabling this, the user sees the list of all of the books\' bookmarks instead of just the last accessed book.</string>
  <string name="search_bookmarks">This is a hint shown in the search text field on the bookmark screen.</string>
  <string name="switch_tabs">This is the title of a menu item that lets the user switch between tabs.</string>
  <string name="close_all_tabs">* This is the content description for a floating action button on the tabs screen.\n* User can remove all opened tabs by clicking this button.</string>
  <string name="pending_state">This is used in text to inform the user current state of downloading is pending.</string>
  <string name="running_state">This is used in text to inform the user current state of downloading is in progress.</string>
  <string name="complete">This is used in text to inform the user current state of downloading is complete.</string>
  <string name="paused_state">This is used in text to inform the user current state of downloading is paused.</string>
  <string name="failed_state">* It is a text shown on the download screen.\n* It is the download status shown upon failure.\n* Here %s will be replaced dynamically.</string>
  <string name="save">{{Identical|Save}}</string>
  <string name="note">{{Identical|Note}}</string>
  <string name="wiki_article_title">It is the title\'s hint on the add-note page.</string>
  <string name="ext_storage_permission_rationale_add_note">This is used in a toast to inform the user that storage access is required for saving notes.</string>
  <string name="ext_storage_write_permission_denied_add_note">This is used in the toast to inform users without storage access notes can not be saved.</string>
  <string name="note_save_unsuccessful">This is used in the toast to inform the user that there is a failure in saving note.</string>
  <string name="note_delete_successful">This message appears in the \"Android Toast\" as an information message, it shows the user the note is successfully deleted.</string>
  <string name="note_delete_unsuccessful">This is used in the toast to inform the user when there is a failure in deleting notes.</string>
  <string name="note_save_successful">This is used in the toast to inform the user when the note is successfully saved.</string>
  <string name="note_save_error_storage_not_writable">It is the toast\'s text shown on the note dialog screen when a user tries to save a note but the external storage is not available for read and write.</string>
  <string name="note_share_error_file_missing">It is the toast\'s text shown on the note dialog screen when a user tries to save a note but the note file does not exist.</string>
  <string name="note_share_app_chooser_title">It is the title of the share intent dialog when the share menu item is clicked on the note screen.</string>
  <string name="confirmation_alert_dialog_message">It is the alert dialog\'s message when a user cancels the note edit screen without saving the changes.</string>
  <string name="delete_notes_confirmation_msg">It is the alert dialog\'s title when a user selects the delete all menu item on the note screen.</string>
  <string name="ext_storage_permission_not_granted">It is the snackbar\'s message when a user tries to delete all notes but the app does not have access to storage permission.</string>
  <string name="notes_deletion_successful">It is the snackbar\'s message when a user successfully deletes all notes via the delete all menu item on the note page.</string>
  <string name="notes_deletion_unsuccessful">It is the snackbar\'s message when a user tries to delete all notes but some files could not be deleted.</string>
  <string name="books_count">%d Identical|Book</string>
  <string name="discovery_initiated">It is a toast\'s message shown on the file-sharing screen when a user clicks on the search menu item to find nearby devices.</string>
  <string name="discovery_failed">It is a toast\'s message shown on the file-sharing screen when finding nearby devices fail to initialize.</string>
  <string name="severe_loss_error">This is toast\'s message when a user\'s wifi P2P gets disconnected from another device.</string>
  <string name="connection_failed">This is toast\'s message when a user fails to connect to another device via wifi P2P.</string>
  <string name="permission_rationale_location">This is dialog\'s message when a user is trying to search nearby devices but the app does not have access to location permission.</string>
  <string name="permission_refused_location">It is a toast\'s message shown when a user tries to share zim files but the app does not have access to location permission.</string>
  <string name="permission_refused_storage">It is a toast\'s message shown when a user tries to share zim files but the app does not have access to storage permission.</string>
  <string name="request_enable_location">It is a dialog\'s message shown when a user tries to share zim files but location service is not enabled.</string>
  <string name="discovery_needs_location">It is a toast\'s message shown when a user tries to search nearby devices but the location service is not enabled.</string>
  <string name="request_enable_wifi">It is a toast\'s message shown when a user tries to search nearby devices but the wifi service is not enabled.</string>
  <string name="discovery_needs_wifi">It is a toast\'s message shown when a user cancels the EnableWifiP2pServices dialog as the wifi service is not enabled.</string>
  <string name="transfer_to">* It is the confirmation dialog message shown when a user selects the peer device when sharing the zim files.\n* Here %s will be replaced by the peer device name.</string>
  <string name="device_not_cooperating">It is the message shown to the sender when the receiver does not accept the transfer prompt when sharing the zim files.</string>
  <string name="file_transfer_complete">It is the toast message shown to the sender when the zim files transfer completes successfully.</string>
  <string name="error_during_transfer">It is the toast message shown to the sender when the zim files transfer fails.</string>
  <string name="error_transferring">It is the toast message shown to the sender with the file names of failed transferred files while sharing zim files via Wifi P2P.\n* Here %s will be replaced by the file names.</string>
  <string name="get_content_from_nearby_device">It is a menu item title in the library screen which takes the user to the receive files screen.</string>
  <string name="search_for_peers">It is a menu item title in the receive files screen which searches for nearby devices.</string>
  <string name="your_device">It is the text in the receive files screen which tells the user about their device name.</string>
  <string name="nearby_devices">It is the text in the receive files screen which tells the user about their nearby devices.</string>
  <string name="no_devices_found">It is a toast message shown on the receive files screen when there is no nearby device found.</string>
  <string name="files_for_transfer">It is the text shown on the receive files screen which tells the user about the files being transferred.</string>
  <string name="preparing_files">It is the toast message shown on the receive files screen when files are being prepared for transfer.</string>
  <string name="performing_handshake">It is the toast message shown on the receive files screen when the sender selects a peer device to connect.</string>
  <string name="status">{{Identical|Status}}</string>
  <string name="pref_clear_all_notes_summary">It is a text description shown on the settings screen that tells the user that selecting this option will clear all notes from all articles.</string>
  <string name="pref_clear_all_notes_title">It is a text title shown on the settings screen and it is used to clear all notes on all articles.</string>
  <string name="pref_allow_to_read_or_write_zim_files_on_sd_card">It is a text description shown on the settings screen and it allows the user to give the app access to file and media permission so the app can read and write zim files.</string>
  <string name="pref_text_zoom_summary">Tell the user that this preference changes the text size in 25% increments.</string>
  <string name="tag_pic">Appears as a tag next to the entry of an item (book) in the Library view of the Android app. It means that this item has images.</string>
  <string name="tag_vid">{{Identical|Vid}}</string>
  <string name="tag_text_only">{{Identical|Text Only}}</string>
  <string name="tag_short_text">{{Identical|Short Text}}</string>
  <string name="storage_permission_denied">It is a dialog title shown on the home page that tells the user that the storage permission has been denied.</string>
  <string name="grant_read_storage_permission">* It is a dialog message shown on the home page that tells the user that the app requires the ability to read storage to function. \n* It also asks the user to go to settings and enable storage permissions which the user can do from the dialog\'s button.</string>
  <string name="go_to_settings">This is used in the start server dialog and leads the user to mobile hotspot settings when pressed</string>
  <string name="no_results">{{Identical|No result}}</string>
  <string name="no_bookmarks">This means \"there are no bookmarks\"</string>
  <string name="no_history">This appears as a text message when there is no history present to show to the user.</string>
  <string name="device_default">* It is a text title shown on the settings screen when the currently selected language is the \'device default\'.\n\n* It is the first text entry in the languages list shown on the settings screen\'s language dialog when the user is selecting the language for the app. Upon selection, this sets the app language as the device\'s default.</string>
  <string name="delete_history">Ask if the user wants to delete all history items.</string>
  <string name="delete_selected_history">Ask if the user wants to delete a number of selected history items.</string>
  <string name="delete_bookmarks">Ask if the user wants to delete all bookmarks.</string>
  <string name="delete_selected_bookmarks">Ask if the user wants to delete a number of selected bookmarks.</string>
  <string name="on">This is used in the settings screen to turn on the night mode.</string>
  <string name="off">This is used in the settings screen to turn off the night mode.</string>
  <string name="auto">This is used in the settings screen to turn the night mode on or off automatically depending upon the system settings of the phone.</string>
  <string name="send_report">It is a text description on the help screen which tells the user that they can send a diagnostic report by selecting it.</string>
  <string name="crash_checkbox_file_system">It is a checkbox title in the Diagnostic report screen which tells the user that they will be sending file system details while sending the diagnostic report.</string>
  <string name="diagnostic_report">It is the screen title for the Diagnostic report screen.</string>
  <string name="diagnostic_report_message">It is a text on the Diagnostic report screen which is asking the user to send all the details seen as checkboxes on the screen.</string>
  <string name="percentage">{{Identical|%d%%}}</string>
  <string name="pref_text_zoom_title">It is a text title in the settings screen which tells the user that they can change the zoom level of texts in the reader.</string>
  <string name="search_open_in_new_tab">* It is a dialog message shown on the reader screen when the user long presses a link.\n* It asks if the user wants to open that specific link in a new tab.</string>
  <string name="reader">The title of the fragment/place where books are read.</string>
  <string name="no_open_book">Tell the user that they have not opened a book.</string>
  <string name="open_library">{{Doc-important|This means \"Open the library\". \"Open\" is a verb. This doesn\'t mean \"An open library\".}}\nThe action of opening the library destination, used on a button.</string>
  <string name="tab_restored">Tell the user that a tab has been restored.</string>
  <string name="tabs_restored">This is used in the snack bar, to inform users all tabs are restored.</string>
  <string name="open_drawer">This is a label text for opening the \"Navigation Drawer\".</string>
  <string name="close_drawer">This is a label text for closing the \"Navigation Drawer\".</string>
  <string name="how_to_update_content">This message appears in the help screen as an information title to tell users how they can update the content.</string>
  <string name="update_content_description">This message appears in the help screen as an informative description to briefly explain to the users how they can update the content.</string>
  <string name="all_files_permission_needed">* It is a dialog title shown when the user switches to the library screen. \n* It is telling user that all files permission is required by the app and is a prompt to allow that permission.</string>
  <string name="all_files_permission_needed_message">* It is a dialog message shown when the user switches to the library screen. \n* It is telling the user that in order to access/read zim files from the storage, the app needs to have All Files permission.</string>
  <string name="allowed">This currently appears under the \"Allow to read and write ZIM files on SD card\" preference title</string>
  <string name="not_allowed">This currently appears under the \"Allow to read and write ZIM files on SD card\" preference title</string>
  <string name="denied_internet_permission_message">This is used in the toast, to inform the user please enable their wifi to download the content.</string>
  <string name="android_directory_seperator">{{Ignored}}</string>
  <string name="select_folder">This is used in the dialog as a title message, to tell the user, to select a folder to use the external storage.</string>
  <string name="system_unable_to_grant_permission_message">This is used in a toast to inform the user that the system is unable to grant permission.</string>
  <string name="allow">{{identical|Allow}}</string>
  <string name="swipe_down_for_library">* It is text information shown on the download screen.\n* It is telling the user that they can load content by swiping down on the screen.</string>
  <string name="no_notes">* This shows as a text message that can be found on the Notes screen. \n* When there are no notes found to show to the user.</string>
  <string name="notes_from_all_books">* This is used in the switch as a title text, which can be found in the Notes screen.\n* By enabling this user views the notes list which is saved in all books.</string>
  <string name="search_notes">This is used in the search view as a hint message that can be found in the notes screen.</string>
  <string name="choose_your_action">* This is used in the dialog as a title text.\n* It means to choose an action from the given option.</string>
  <string name="open_note">This is used in the dialog as a button text, by clicking this button saved note will open.</string>
  <string name="open_article">* This is used in the dialog as a button text, by clicking this button saved article will open.\n* This informs the user this is for opening the article.</string>
  <string name="delete_note_dialog_message">This is used in the dialog, to inform the user, notes will not be deleted from your storage.</string>
  <string name="delete_selected_notes">This is used in the dialog as a dialog title, to take confirmation from the user he wants to delete the selected notes in a list.</string>
  <string name="download_tts_language_title">This is used in the dialog, to use read aloud feature, you need to download this language.</string>
  <string name="download_tts_language_message">This is used in the dialog, to explain the instruction on how he can download the required language.</string>
  <string name="external_link_copied_message">This is used in the toast when the external link is copied successfully to the clipboard.</string>
  <string name="read_aloud_service_channel_name">Name of the notification channel used for the real aloud persistent notification. Can be found in Android notification settings for Kiwix app.</string>
  <string name="read_aloud_channel_description">Description of the notification channel used for the read aloud persistent notification. Can be found in Android notification settings for Kiwix app, inside the \"Read Aloud Service Channel\" details screen.</string>
  <string name="read_aloud_running">* Informs the user that the Read Aloud is currently running.\n* This appears in the \"Android Notification\" as a notification description message.</string>
  <string name="backward_history">Informs the user that the currently visible history list is backward history.</string>
  <string name="forward_history">Informs the user that the currently visible history list is forward history.</string>
  <string name="clear_all_navigation_history_message">This message appears in the \"Android Dialog\" as a confirmation message, to take confirmation from the user that he wants to clear all navigation history.</string>
  <string name="navigation_history_cleared">This message appears in the \"Android Toast\" as a confirmation message. When navigation history is cleared successfully.</string>
  <string name="go_to_settings_label">This is a text label, by clicking on this text user navigates to the app settings on their device.</string>
  <string name="request_notification_permission_message">This message appears in the \"Android Dialog\" as an information message. When the user tries to run any functionality which requires notification access but the app does not have that access, then this message shows to the user to give notification access.</string>
  <string name="empty_string">{{Ignored}}</string>
</resources>
